{
    "id": "8c257a145fde42e5a7340f4c5fa68621",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The car is running more smoothly ………………… .. it had a service.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… Mike is married, he is much more responsible.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Now that",
                "Such that"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t settled the question of ………………… I’ll go back home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "whether"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They held the meeting on a holiday ………………….. everyone would be free to attend.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in order for",
                "in order that"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. she hadn’t prepared for the presentation, she did a commendable job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Although"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. I told you earlier, the meeting has been postponed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Like"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "My doctor told me to avoid fatty foods …………………… .. burgers and cheese.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "such as"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It was ………………… a loud noise ………………….. to wake everybody in the whole neighborhood.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "such ....as...",
                "so...that.."
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… much he eats, he never gets fat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "However",
                "Whatever"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He accepted the challenge ……………………… he had been waiting for it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "as though"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}